(This story is entirely fictional)
(I spent three months)
(playing her one and only soulmate.)
(I listened to her crying)
(and validated her anger.)
(She hit me again.)
(She said I only exist)
(to be men's lapdog.)
(She said I embarrassed her.)
(She called me
a useless piece of trash.)
(She doesn't care about you.)
(Based on novel Doctor Qin: Executer)
(She only cares about her perfect work.)
I know.
But what am I supposed to do?
I hate her.
But I can't leave her.
(I planted a seed in her mind.)
(Rebellion is rebirth.)
(I taught her
how to cut Su Shi where it hurts.)
(What Su Shi fears most
is Su Tang turning out just like her.)
(And all Su Tang has to do)
(is make that deepest fear)
(real)
(and shove it in her face.)
(She's gone mad.)
(A madwoman)
(can't control you anymore.)
(Now)
(it's your turn to control her.)
=Doctor Qin: Executer=
=Episode 22=
Chew the toothpaste a little longer.
It works better that way.
Remember what you're supposed to do.
Tang, time to eat.
Tang.
Tang?
Tang!
Tang.
Tang, what are you doing?
Where's the money?
Where did you put the money?
East corner of the cat house.
Under the third flower pot.
This is all you'll ever be!
Who are you?
Jin Xiaoxue?
You witch, you corrupted Tang!
Let me out!
Then get on your knees and beg.
Just like you taught
those girls back then.
Told them
how to kneel
to survive.
I was teaching them to face reality!
Don't worry.
I won't kill you.
I'll let you die at the hands
of the most failed piece of work
you ever created.
Tang,
open the cage.
Don't let her mess with your head.
She's a demon.
Don't believe her.
Tang.
Let's kill her together.
Su Tang.
She's lying to you again.
Did you forget
how she locked you in the cage?
And how she called you spineless?
Tang.
I'm your mom.
The motherly love she talks about
is just chains and cages.
Look at her eyes.
There's no love in them.
Just control.
Kill her.
Kill her and you're free.
Kill this demon
who's been tying you down
your whole life
with chains and curses.
Don't listen to her.
Don't let her mess with your head.
Kill her.
I'll take you away.
I'll take you somewhere with no pain,
somewhere you can start over.
I'm your mom.
(Did you forget
how she locked you in the cage?)
(The motherly love she talks about)
(is just chains and cages.)
(Kill her and you're free.)
(Kill her.)
(Fan A71954)
What about Su Tang?
Why her?
That was an accident.
I never
wanted her dead.
But
who's to say Su Shi
would definitely get in the cage?
What if she ran?
So
I messed with Su Shi's car.
A second layer of insurance.
How's Su Tang doing now?
She's drowning in regret and guilt.
I want her
to identify me in court.
I want to apologize to her face to face.
Mr. Qin, your takeout.
Just put it here.
I never really liked fish balls before.
Until you put them in my bowl.
Officer Qin.
Actually, lots of times
I dreamed
it was you putting the cuffs on me.
Lots of times.
Ms. Song, is there something you need?
I...
Chen, go do your thing.
Ms. Song, what are you...?
I... I want to see my daughter.
But she's under interrogation.
No visitors allowed.
Look.
The moment visits are allowed,
I'll let you know.
Do you guys feed her?
Of course.
Qin Ming ordered takeout for her today.
Good.
I think
I've seen that boy before.
He seems nice.
I'll get the kids' wedding sorted
when I get a chance.
It'd be better
if he ordered some bubble tea.
She loves that stuff.
I remember you had a wild imagination
back in school.
I still do.
So I tried my best to learn.
After all, I deal with a miserable world
every single day.
On Zhang Xiaodong's food chain,
Le Tianyi was the most vicious,
hungriest wild dog.
He enjoyed the thrill
of tearing the weak apart.
Because that way,
it let him forget
the humiliation
of being controlled by the strong.
So you went to Wang Xuan?
I watched her for a long time.
She'd been broken down by years of
mental abuse and domestic violence.
If I just told her to kill someone,
she wouldn't dare.
So
I had to shatter
the last bit of hope
she was holding onto.
The old man smiled and said,
"When fate blocks one road,
it often leaves another."
(I knew)
(she'd gone numb
from being humiliated for so long.)
(Le Tianyi's cheating on her)
(wasn't enough for her
to make up her mind.)
Keep watching.
(House Sale Contract)
Le Tianyi's moving his assets.
He's planning to leave you with nothing.
He's even taking away
the last bit of security
you and Niu have.
You're still waiting for him
to come back
and save your daughter?
(Longfan Second People's Hospital;
Outpatient Medical Record)
This is the best brain tumor specialist
in the country.
He's the only one
who can do Niu's surgery.
This is for the surgery.
Why
are you helping me?
I'm not helping you.
I'm just giving you a choice.
You either watch your daughter die
and get thrown out,
or you take back what's yours
and give Niu a way to live.
Location.
Tools.
Even what you say
to the cops after he's dead.
I've figured all of this out for you.
All you have to do
is put a towel over his face
the next time he raises his hand to you.
You've been investigating me this long.
You should know I'm not an idiot.
Consider this money
a loan.
But I have one condition.
I'll take care of everything for Niu,
until she's an adult.
A few years of your life
for her safety for the rest of hers.
Do you think
that's a fair trade?
You and Wang Xuan
killed Le Tianyi together?
No.
I changed my mind at the last minute.
I'm on my way to the police station!
I'll tell you everything I...
(Open 24 Hours)
Get out.
What's wrong?
You should go.
Niu needs her mom right now.
Let me go!
Now!
I said let me go!
(High in the tower,)
(the hypocrite builds their nest,)
(grinding their struggles into steps,)
(and boiling their tears into soup.)
(This man)
(is like a pig that can never
be fed enough!)
Help!
Help me!
Wang Xuan's a victim too.
I didn't want her hands
stained with blood.
What about you?
I don't care.
I just want to wipe out
those scumbags fast.
You paid for Niu's surgery?
That day, when I ran into you
while I was picking up Niu,
you already suspected me, didn't you?
I was sure whoever came
to pick her up was the killer.
Until you gave me
another perfect excuse.
Turns out
your suspicion was right.
Where did you get that kind of money?
Put it in.
Hurry!
Okay, okay.
You can probably guess.
It's fine.
Hey, let me tell you.
I run this place.
If anything comes up, you come to me.
I've got your back.
We're from
the Longfan Public Security Bureau.
You're coming with us.
Move.
No. I...
Qin.
Jin Keke was right.
We brought him back.
Tell us about Zhang Xiaodong.
He liked crocodiles.
So I gave him what he wanted.
How did you get him out there alone?
Zhang Xiaodong?
Easy.
♪In the fog of the long night♪
♪Who hid the truth?♪
♪Good and evil blur♪
♪Lies whisper, sinking
into the riverbed of human nature♪
♪Hearts are like nameless alleys♪
♪The false facade softens
every smile on their faces♪
♪Sunset washes over the old wall♪
♪Milk tea cools on the stone steps♪
♪Sea wind tugs at your sleeve♪
♪Unspoken words just flee and fade♪
♪The marks on the desk
have faded yellow♪
♪I turned around,
and a gunshot rang out♪
♪No one can truly feel another's pain♪
♪The wind is cold,
a fading shadow sways♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪A bullet pierces the spring night♪
♪You sink into the vast crowd♪
♪Years later, when we meet again♪
♪Don't mention this moonlit night♪
♪The waves smooth
two lines of footprints♪
♪Half a cup of sweetness
sinks into the sand♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪Wind back to shore,
clouds back to hills♪
♪We stop here in this night♪
♪This is the past, the only,
the last look back♪
♪One gunshot echoes through half a life♪